<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>alpinaraid on Léo Krebs</title>
    <link>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/tags/alpinaraid/</link>
    <description>Recent content in alpinaraid on Léo Krebs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/tags/alpinaraid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alpinaraid 10</title>
      <link>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-10/</guid>
      <description>Alpinaraid 10 This last set from the Alpinaraid series regroup all pictures I took during our trip to come back home. We drove by the Gorges du Verdon, which is where I took the different pictures.
It is a beautiful, natural place, that was unfortunately a bit dry when we were there.
Photo details Rollei 35S + Fujifilm Superia Xtra</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpinaraid 9</title>
      <link>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-9/</guid>
      <description>Alpinaraid 9 Finish line! The first image was taken at the Menton Beach, where we finished the Alpinaraid. It was an amazing experience, I saw places, sceneries and landscapes that I have never seen before.
Second picture was taken during our trip along the Côte d&amp;rsquo;Azur.
Photo details Rollei 35S + Fujifilm Superia Xtra
The scenery from the first picture was so colorful, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t be happier with how the result turned out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpinaraid 8</title>
      <link>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-8/</guid>
      <description>Alpinaraid 8 In this set, I chose three images I took during our stroll in Saint-Véran (one of Europe&amp;rsquo;s most elevated village). It it a peaceful village we enjoyed discovering.
The last image of this set was shot during a downhill in Italy. Cows were on the other side of the lake.
Photo details Rollei 35S + Fujifilm Superia Xtra
I really like how the water turns out with this roll of film.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpinaraid 7</title>
      <link>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-7/</guid>
      <description>Alpinaraid 7 The first image was taken at the Caserme Della Bandia. It was very interesting to explore these ruins perched so high in the mountains.
Second and third pictures were shot during our visit of the Vallée de Névache: one of the most beautiful valley we took during this journey.
Photo details Rollei 35S + Fujifilm Superia Xtra</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpinaraid 6</title>
      <link>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-6/</guid>
      <description>Alpinaraid 6 The two pictures from this set are also among my favourites. They were taken at the Colle di Sommeiller, at 3000 m altitude. We were enjoying the landscape after going uphill about 800 m of positive elevation. Notice how the hood is a bit open: we called it the &amp;lsquo;race mode&amp;rsquo;, the goal was to cool-off the engine bay a bit faster.
Photo details Rollei 35S + Fujifilm Superia Xtra</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpinaraid 5</title>
      <link>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-5/</guid>
      <description>Alpinaraid 5 The first picture in this set is my favourite from the whole journey. I was lucky enough to take out the camera before the cloud could go further away, and managed to shoot it with the sunset hitting the grass in the foreground. It was taken at the Rifugio dell&amp;rsquo;Assietta.
The second and third images were probably taken during cool-off breaks for the car, after long uphill roads (as seen in the background of image #3).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpinaraid 4</title>
      <link>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-4/</guid>
      <description>Alpinaraid 4 The two pictures were taken on the shore of Lago Di Rochemolles, on our way to the Colle Di Sommeiller.
Photo details Rollei 35S + Fujifilm Superia Xtra
Focusing is a bit tricky with the Rollei, as it is made with a ring around the lens, according to a value the photographer has to measure (in my case, it was measured with stride length).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpinaraid 3</title>
      <link>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-3/</guid>
      <description>Alpinaraid 3 In this set, I decided to show various landscapes taken during the journey.
The first image is one of my favourite from the two rolls I shot during the adventure. It was 5 minutes before we ended surronded by the clouds seen in the background, at the Colle delle Finestre (2176 m).
Second image was taken during an uphill in an old italian military track.
Third one was shot in the morning at Camping Le Gravelotte, just after our first camp night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpinaraid 2</title>
      <link>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-2/</guid>
      <description>Alpinaraid 2 Here are the first pictures I took of our Genesis Blue Peugeot 205.
The first image was shot at the Lac du Mont-Cenis. It really looks like we were all alone in this beautiful scenery.
Second picture was taken somewhere in Italy, during a mountain pass downhill.
Last photo was taken at Col du Glandon (1924 m).
Photo details Rollei 35S + Fujifilm Superia Xtra
I think the use of the Superia Xtra roll was a great choice for its pastel looking feel in the blue and green range.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpinaraid 1</title>
      <link>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://precious-platypus-594d72.netlify.app/work/alpinaraid/alpinaraid-1/</guid>
      <description>Alpinaraid 1 This is it. After months of preparation of our Peugeot 205, we finally started our journey into the French and Italian Alps.
In this 10 set series, you can find the film photographies that I took during the whole adventure.
In this first set Alpinaraid 1, photos 1 and 2 were taken on the border of the Annecy Lake, in the early morning, on our way to the starting point at Col de la Madeleine (2000 m).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
