<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>urban on Léo Krebs</title>
    <link>https://leokr.fr/tags/urban/</link>
    <description>Recent content in urban on Léo Krebs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://leokr.fr/tags/urban/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Abandonned convent</title>
      <link>https://leokr.fr/work/urban/urbex-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leokr.fr/work/urban/urbex-3/</guid>
      <description>Abandonned convent A small convent in the alsacian wineyards. Besides a cat that scared us at the end, it was a very calm and relaxing visit. Lots of small empty rooms, a chapel, kitchen, interior garden.
Last picture was to finish the roll: we stumbled across some hang-gliders flying.
Photo details Second part of my BGC PHC-50 film roll. I think the blacks are really deep, and the 50 ISO + use of flash really made these look dramatic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abandonned hotel in the mountains 2/2</title>
      <link>https://leokr.fr/work/urban/urbex-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leokr.fr/work/urban/urbex-2/</guid>
      <description>Abandonned hotel in the mountains Second part of the &amp;lsquo;abandonned hotel in the moutain&amp;rsquo; series: a hotel on top of the mountains, built in the 1920s and closed since 1994.
Inside: a pool, dancefloor, kitchen, rooms, and more. There is a second building which unfortunately burnt down.
The place is quite well known from exploration enjoyers, hence some artists beautifully decorated some of the rooms.
The first picture shows a graffiti of a masked man The second picture depicts a fully decorated room with music scores, pins, and typewritten letters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abandonned hotel in the mountains 1/2</title>
      <link>https://leokr.fr/work/urban/urbex-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leokr.fr/work/urban/urbex-1/</guid>
      <description>Abandonned hotel in the mountains First part of the &amp;lsquo;abandonned hotel in the moutain&amp;rsquo; series: a hotel on top of the mountains, built in the 1920s and closed since 1994.
Inside: a pool, dancefloor, kitchen, rooms, and more. There is a second building which unfortunately burnt down (last picture).
Photo details First part of my BGC PHC-50 film roll. The Yashica ZoomTec 90 did a great job getting shots of this piece of history atop of the mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helsinki 1/3</title>
      <link>https://leokr.fr/work/urban/helsinki-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leokr.fr/work/urban/helsinki-1/</guid>
      <description>Helsinki 1 First series of pictures from my Helsinki trip. I tried to capture there the city&amp;rsquo;s architecture. There are some notable buildings:
Second picture is the exterior of the Amos Rex museum Fourth picture is the Kansallismuseo Fifth picture is the front of the Helsingin tuomiokirkko, the city&amp;rsquo;s Cathedral. Photo details This trip was the first time I used the Rollei 35S, which was perfectly adapted to travel due to its pocket form factor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helsinki 2/3</title>
      <link>https://leokr.fr/work/urban/helsinki-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leokr.fr/work/urban/helsinki-2/</guid>
      <description>Helsinki 2 Second series of pictures from my Helsinki trip. This time, it is consacred to the University&amp;rsquo;s Botanical garden (Kaisaniemen kasvitieteellinen puutarha).
Photo details For these pictures, I had to play with the focus ring on the Rollei 35S, to get the focus on objects not in the infinite range. It is a bit imprecise, but some pictures turned out great.
Rollei 35S + Kodak Tri-X 400.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helsinki 3/3</title>
      <link>https://leokr.fr/work/urban/helsinki-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leokr.fr/work/urban/helsinki-3/</guid>
      <description>Helsinki 3 Last series of pictures from my Helsinki trip. Some other great pieces of architecture:
Second picture is the Finnish Parliament (Eduskusta) Third picture depicts the Vesikko submarine, it was taken on the island of Suomenlinna Photo details I had to edit the plane wing picture to remove some stains and noises, which I normally don&amp;rsquo;t do because they are part of the picture when doing film photography. But since they were quite large, I had to work around to make it viewable.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
